As we discussed with the box model,
正如我们在盒模型中提到的
all elements are read and displayed by the browser as rectangles.
所有浏览器中的元素都可以被视为一个矩形
The CSS display property sets the behavior for how each
CSS 显示属性（display）用来定义每个矩形元素
of these rectangles participates in the flow of elements.
在一系列元素流中的行为
Each element can have an inside display and an outside display property.
每个元素可以有一些内部和外部的显示属性
We'll be focusing on the inside display in later lessons which determines
我们会在后面的课程中重点关注内部显示属性
the positioning behavior of the children elements inside of an element,
它用来决定元素内部的子元素的定位行为
and this is where flex and CSS grid come into play.
这时就会涉及 flex 弹性盒子 和 CSS grid 网格
But for now, let's focus on the outer display which
现在 我们先关注外部显示属性
determines how the element itself flows with other elements.
也就是元素自身和其他元素之间如何显示的问题
This will be easier to conceptualize with a demonstration which we'll do in a second.
在稍后的演示例子中 你可以更轻松地理解它们的概念
But first, let's just take a quick look at the most common values for outer CSS display.
不过首先 我们先快速浏览一些最常用的 CSS 显示属性
There's display inline, there's display inline-block,
有 inline 属性、inline-block 属性、
display block, and display none.
block 属性、还有 none 属性
So here, you can see I have set up four elements with the
这里 你可以看到我们放置了 4 个元素
class "box" and right now the CSS is just a background color,
它们都有一个 box 的类名 目前 CSS 样式仅为一个背景颜色
a color, and a little margin.
字体颜色和一点点外边距
So let's see what happens if we set the display here to inline.
现在我们试着把 display 属性设置为 inline 来看看会发生什么
Very different, and what about if we change it to block?
和之前完全不一样了 如果设置为 block 属性呢 ?
You can see block stretches over an entire line in the browser.
你可以看到 block 撑满了浏览器的整行的空间
It takes up a block.
也就是一整块空间
Inline on the other hand only takes up the amount of
Inline 属性则相反 它只占用
space that it needs given the content that's inside of it.
它内部内容所需要的空间
So inline just takes up how long each of these words are.
所以 inline 属性元素只占有这些单词长度的空间
Coincidental, it's the largest block because it's the largest word.
在这里 Coincidental 是最大的元素 因为它内部的单词长度最长
Whereas when we did block,
而当我们切换成 block 的话
you can see that regardless of how long any of these are,
你可以看到无论里面的内容多长
each of them take up an entire line on the screen.
每个元素都会占用整行的屏幕空间
So what do you think will happen when I use display none property?
那如果是 none 属性又会发生什么情况呢 ?
Ready? It displays nothing which may
它隐藏掉了所有元素
seem a little counter-intuitive to you but it can come in handy
你可能会觉得有一点鸡肋 但实际上非常有用
because there are times where we want an element to be there
因为有些时候你想要在需要的地方放置一个元素
when we need it but we don't want it to be there all the time.
但是你不想要它一直在那
So having display none let's us not get rid of
所以设置 display=none 可以让我们既不用
the element but also not have it take up space in the DOM as we've talked about.
删除元素 又可以让它不占用我们的页面空间
So it doesn't disrupt the flow of other elements.
这样就不会干扰到其他元素在结构中的位置
The display property can give you a lot of creative options
display 属性给了你很多选项
especially as we continue to learn more about flex and grid.
尤其是在过后我们学习弹性盒子和网格的时候
For now, why don't you jump in and see if you could do some of
现在 为什么不试着用刚才我们学习到的 display 属性
your own work around these different displays? Good luck.
自己做一些有趣的东西呢？祝你好运